conceptcarz.com 2006-06-16

# Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy**

* * *

**Normal Viewing Information**

As you visit the site, Concept Carz does not acquire or collect any personal information about you. Your name, address, phone number, and email address all remain your private properties. Concept Carz does, however, collect information which is specific to how you use the site. Concept Carz servers note details such as the type of browser you use, and your IP address. This information is obtained solely for Concept Carz's measurements of the site's effectiveness. 

**The Cookie Principle**

Concept Carz uses cookies to improve your Web browsing experience. The cookie that is stored on your machine contains information about the username that you have chosen for this website. 

Users who sign up for and use advanced features of Concept Carz, will be asked for additional information including email address and possibly demographic information. BECAUSE WE PROTECT OUR USERS FROM SPAMMERS, Concept Carz DOES NOT SELL THIS INFORMATION TO EXTERNAL COMPANIES. Email addresses are used purely to verify the user's true identity and prevent fraud, while demographic information is used purely for the purpose of targeting ads and measuring their effectiveness on behalf of Concept Carz clients and customers. 

  * We caution you against giving out personally identifiable information (such as social security numbers, credit card numbers, names and addresses, telephone numbers, driver license numbers) to strangers online, which may be used for illegal or harmful purposes. 

**Advertisers**

We use an outside ad company to display ads on the Sites. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of the Sites, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad company, and we do not have access to this information. 

**Consent**

By using this web site, you consent to the collection and use of information by Concept Carz. Changes to our privacy policy will be posted to this page, so you may be updated as soon as possible. If you have any questions or comments regarding this policy, please e-mail us at dan@conceptcarz.com. 

**Our Commitment to Privacy**

Our Privacy Policy was developed as an extension of our commitment to combine the highest-quality products and services with the highest level of integrity in dealing with our clients and partners. The Policy is designed to assist you in understanding how we collect, use and safeguard the personal information you provide to us and to assist you in making informed decisions when using our site and our products and services. This statement will be continuously assessed against new technologies, business practices and our customers' needs. 

**Sharing Information with Affiliates**

From time to time you may notice offers from outside companies advertised on our Web site. We take measures to select product or service providers that are responsible and afford privacy protections to their customers. However, we cannot make any representations about the practices and policies of these companies. 

|     
---|---
